(upbeat rock music)
♪ In the not too distant future ♪
♪ Way down in Deep 13 ♪
♪ Dr. Forrester and TV's Frank ♪
♪ Were hatching an evil scheme ♪
♪ They hired a temp by the name of Mike ♪
♪ Just a regular Joe they didn't like ♪
♪ Their experiment
needed a good test case ♪
♪ So they conked him on the noggin ♪
♪ And they shot him into space ♪
- [Mike] Let me go.
♪ We'll send him cheesy movies ♪
♪ The worst we can find ♪
♪ He'll have to sit and watch them all ♪
♪ And we'll monitor his mind ♪
♪ Now keep in mind Mike can't control ♪
♪ Where the movies begin or end ♪
♪ He'll try to keep his sanity ♪
♪ With the help of his robot friends ♪
♪ Robot roll call ♪
♪ Cambot, Gypsy, Tom, Servo, Crow ♪
♪ If you're wondering how
he eats and breathes ♪
♪ And other science facts ♪
♪ Just repeat to yourself
it's just a show ♪
♪ I should really just relax ♪
♪ For "Mystery Science Theater 3000" ♪
(metal door clanking)
(space station beeping)
(door whooshing)
(door zipping)
(door clanking)
- See, I don't know what my area code is
'cause I'm up in the Milky
Way for crying out loud.
(robots giggling)
- Oh, hi everyone, Tom Servo
here on the Satellite of Love.
And this is my pal Crow.
- Yeah, and that goofy
looking guy back there?
That's Mike Nelson.
He's trying to call his
grandma on the phone.
It's a sweet gesture, isn't it?
But we explained to him
it's not that easy to do
when you're stranded in space.
- Yeah well you guys are never armed
with a stack of calling cards
and a few little tricks like I am.
Hello?
- Wow!
- Hey, get around here, this is it!
- What, you're kidding!
(telephone ringing)
You actually got your
grandma on the phone?
- This is my grandma.
(phone ringing)
- Well Grandma's a mall walker,
she's probably just getting in right now.
- Right yeah.
- [Grandma] Hello?
- Hello, Grandma, this is
Mike, I'm stranded in space,
you gotta help, you gotta
get someone to help me down!
- [Grandma] Mike, what's that?
Speak up.
- I say, I've been
shanghaied on a satellite,
you gotta get someone to
help me get outta here!
- [Grandma] I'm just
kidding, this is Katherine
and I'm not in right now.
I might be sitting for Tommy's kids
or else I'm at Linda's,
leave a message.
(answering machine beeping)
- Grandma, listen very carefully,
this is Mike, I've been-
(answering machine beeping)
(dial tone buzzing)
(Mike groaning)
That was my only chance.
- Wow that's harsh, huh?
- That's okay, Mike,
we're your family now.
- Yeah.
(telephone buttons beeping)
(upbeat rock music)
- Sprint?
- No.
- Mike, Mike, Mike, Mike.
Oh, you should really make a note of that.
That you got a machine
so that if the bill comes
and we're erroneously
charged for the call,
then you have a paperwork
to back up your claim
that we were charged for the call in error
so that you won't have to
pay for the call, Mike.
- But Crow, you lived
during the Great Depression,
didn't you?
- Oh Backrack and David are calling.
- They are?
- Just push the button.
- Laundry, laundry, oh!
Mike, you would not
believe the day I've had,
I don't know how single parents do it!
Oh I was excited with the
arrival of young Frank but-
- Dr. Raff, come on!
- Clayton's on the phone right now, Frank.
It's a 25 hour a day job
keeping track of Frank.
He's into everything.
Sometimes I think we
both need a little break.
That's why I've invented
the Frankenforcer.
You see, the Frankenforcer
keeps little Frank suspended
in that disorienting no-man's-land
between floor and ceiling.
The mat with the nails jutting out
at a most dangerous angle,
gently discourages Frank
from jumping out of the
Frankenforcer and into Dr. F's hair.
- Wait!
- Just a little minute
Frankie, there you go.
Now Dr. Forester has time
to tabulate and standardize
results of our latest experiment,
postulate new theories
or just get the laundry done
without worrying about this one.
Plus, I've gotten to know
someone very special, me.
(doctor chortling)
Oh, gotta go Mike, we get fussy
if we've been in there
more than a few weeks.
Immature little baby.
- I'm guessing Frank's
in the 90th percentile.
(robots laugh)
- Anyway, let me set the scene here.
You're at your favorite
candlelit restaurant,
spending time with someone very special.
Exchanging lingering glances
over the feta cheese-
- What?
- Laughing low, throaty laughs
over a shared private joke,
fingers entwined.
- Would you just get on with it, Servo?
- And sometimes you just
need your server's attention!
Enter the Waitervator.
(robots laugh)
- I'll be right over here, hi Tad!
- Don't waste your valuable time
trying to get your waiter's attention,
just let the Waitervator
do the dirty work!
- I'll be with you in a moment please,
I'm in the weeds here.
(Crow mumbling)
- Okay, well what do you think, sirs?
- I think you'll be having our special.
A tough stringy entree
called Teenage Strangler.
(grumbling) Frank!
Served with a distasteful
little appetizer about love
or some such slop.
Frank.
I think I'm going to have
to put Frank down for a nap.
Permanently.
(Dr. Forrester grumbles)
Frank.
- No, no, you had three big
bites of my lettuce-wich.
- Yeah, but you had my
cling-peach, so it evened it out.
- I only had a little
taste of your cling-peach,
you don't expect me
- You eat the whole half.
- I'm not going to pay
for your cling-peach.
- I'm not going to have to pay for it.
- Ladies, ladies, we have movie time.
(whoosh)
(robotic door opening)
(clunk)
(bubbles)
(zipping)
(beeping)
(metal door clank)
(clanking)
(old-silent-movie-music)
- [Mike] If you two would just
get together and pay the tab.
- [Servo] Is this love
or is it just rough sex
with Michael Douglas?
- [Crow] Wow. What?
- [Mike] By Paul H.
Landis, who's never known
the touch of a woman.
(romantic 1920's music)
- [Crow] Collaborator Lillian Bilkey,
who's single and lives in a
furnished room with six cats.
- [Mike] Lillian Bilkey.
- [Robot 1] Bilkey.
- [Robot 2] Bilkey
- [Mike] Well, except for
Tom Hanks and Peter Scolari.
(Servo gasping and gulping)
- [Servo] Out of my way, I want to catch
the end of Bobby Hackett's trumpet solo.
- [Crow] Miss Channing, there's
an Eve Herington to see you.
- [Mike] t's like Van
Goghs's room in Arles.
- [Servo] So, um, where's Waldo?
- [Mike] Ah, he's under the bed.
- [Crow] Geez, how many
time was she held back?
(Servo chuckles)
- Hi, Peg.
- [Mike] Hi, Mom.
- God, you look more excited
than I've ever seen you before
and that's say something.
(Crow meows and hisses)
- You'll never guess.
I got engaged to Joe.
We're going to be married
at the end of the semester.
Right after Joe graduates.
- What?
You've only been going steady
with him for a couple of months.
- Exactly three months and three days.
- [Servo] Love has made me anal.
(Servo laughs)
- But, Peg, are you going
to drop out of college
before you graduate?
I mean, you've only
got another year to go.
- Oh, Liz, everyone isn't
as slow as you and Andy.
- [Crow] Besides you're a Romulan.
- I want to get married in June.
- [Mike] Mm, get the cops.
- Joe has been told he's got a good chance
of getting a job at a
pro-football team this summer.
- As a water boy.
- He'll still would make that.
- Are you going to phone your mom and dad
about getting engaged.
- [Crow] Actually they're married already.
Oh, oh I see.
- I'm scared stiff about
what mother will say.
She'll raise the roof.
I think I'll send a telegram instead.
- Don't be silly, Peg.
You always talk as though your
mother was an ogre or some-
- [Mike] Well, I've known
her for fifty years.
- Mother will be furious.
Every so often she writes to
ask if I've seen Pete Standard.
You know, just because his father's
a big time real estate man
and he's mother's idea of perfect catch.
- He's just go the the Glen-Gery account.
- Compared to Joe, Pete's so dull.
Joe's so handsome.
- [Crow] Handsome equals not dull.
- [Servo] Ding.
- Honestly, Peg, I don't
know how many times
ever since we were in high school together
I've heard you go on the same
way about some man or other.
- Oh but this is different,
Liz, really it is.
- [Mike] He's anatomically
correct and everything.
- It's the real thing.
- I remember when I first
felt that way about Andy.
- [Servo] At the turn of the century.
- I think about him all the time.
Gosh, Peggy, you just
can't rush into marriage.
- [Crow] Why not?
Julian Roberts did.
- Mm.
- Don't mind my saying this,
but you and Andy seem so, so-
- So old fashioned I suppose you mean?
- [Mike] No, just old.
- Well you've been going
together for a year and half.
Last month, you finally became engaged.
I'm just not like that.
- [Servo] I'm easy.
- Well that's fine,
but are you sure you'll
always been in love
like you are right now?
- [Crow] With somebody sure.
- What do you mean?
- Liz, how can you say such a thing?
- Oh, wait a minute, Peg.
- [Mike] Come here.
- [Liz] Please don't get upset.
All I mean is, are you
sure you see eye to eye
about things like-
- [Servo] The Trade Deficit?
- Well, like money, and children?
- Oh yes.
- [Liz] Or even what's
right and what's wrong.
How do you get along with
each other's families?
- [Mike] Boring.
- [Liz] Supposed your
parents won't approve.
You have to think about these things, Peg.
- [Crow] Look, can we get separate beds?
- As far as I'm concerned,
you don't have to think it
if you've found the right man.
- [Mike] Excuse me, but
that's my boyfriend.
- You better go and send that telegram.
- [Mike] I'm too much in
love to send a telegram.
- [Crow] I love his picture,
maybe some day I'll meet him in person.
No.
- [Servo] Well let's see, if
my, yeah, if my, wait a minute,
if my demands are not
meant, the screams of those
who've wronged me and the
smell of burning flesh
will fill the student, um, union.
- [Liz] Randy, how's the essay coming?
- [Mike] Not so good, Mom.
- Page two?
Not so good.
- [Crow] Will you just lay off?
- No, I can do an engineering
paper in two days, Liz,
but I've been working on this
English assignment for a week.
And nothing.
- Gosh, Andy, you've
got to get your English
or you won't graduate.
- [Servo] Would you just leave me alone.
- Yeah I know.
- Look, why don't we meet
at the library tonight.
- [Servo] Oh, yeah.
- Maybe I can help.
(robots laugh)
- Gee thanks, Liz, that'll be swell.
- [Mike] In form us without a cause.
- [Andy] Hey look the
love birds have arrived.
- [Crow] And they're
leaving their droppings
all over the place.
- Nothing like advertising.
- They got engaged last night.
(robots gasp)
Peggy says they're getting
married right after commencement.
- Married?
- [Servo] It's immoral.
- Boy, Peggy thinks it's all hand-holding
and gazing into each other's eyes.
- [Servo] She doesn't know
about the stench pneumonemia
from the piles of crap-filled diapers and-
- [Crow] And now a firm,
and hearty handclasp.
- [Andy] Those first dates were exciting.
The more I got to know you,
the more I liked what I knew.
Though I supposed I was really intrigued
by the things I didn't know about you.
- [Servo] Like you being
a communist and all.
- [Andy] We seemed to have lots in common.
It was so many things
we could do together.
- [Mike] What the hell was that for?
- Well you were supposed to
cover down the line, I told you.
Come here, look at that.
- [Andy] I wish I could
argue with you there.
- [Crow] But you've emasculated me.
- [Liz] You really enjoy a
good argument, don't you?
I haven't forgotten the
time the Dean's rule
on drinking came out.
(indistinct)
- [Andy] And that was the day
I found out we could argue
like anything and somehow
love each other more.
I thought expulsion was
too stiff a penalty.
One small slip and some guy's
whole life could be changed.
- [Mike] Drinking in college?
I've never heard of that.
- [Liz] I couldn't entirely agree.
Expelling somebody is a
serious thing of course,
but so is drinking in a dorm.
All those people living so close together-
- [Servo] Look would you
just lay off for ten seconds.
- Well, we didn't settle the issue,
but it sure was fun trying.
I wanted to convince you and
you tried to convince me.
(robots laugh)
Though I guessed we became most
convinced about each other.
- [Liv] We must have.
Up until a month a go that
finger looked kind of bare.
Remember?
- [Servo] Naked.
(1920's romantic music)
- [Crow] A (indistinct) zirconia?
You jerk.
[Mike] QVC thank you.
- [Servo] I figured if
like we split it, the cost,
we can afford it.
- [Crow] Gifts given in
dorms, punished by expulsion.
(indistinct)
- [Servo] This I (indistinct) for Patrick.
- Oh, I'm on fire.
- Enough, that's enough.
- [Crow] Honey, I also
got you a subscription
to modern maturity.
- Gosh, it think our folks
were even more excited
than we were.
- [Mike] Yeah, when your
dad got the shot gun down.
- [Peg] Ready to go back to the dorm?
- Hi.
- [Joe] Hi, hi Andy.
- Hey congratulations, you
two, I just heard the news.
- Oh thanks, Andy.
(robots laugh)
(80's action music)
- Have you found a place
to live around here?
- Oh, I don't think we have
to worry about anything.
We'll just find a little
apartment somewhere.
- Peggy.
- [Servo] It's the heat, run.
- Mother, Dad.
- Hi, darling.
- [Crow] Oh poopie.
- [Peg] What are you doing here?
- We got your telegram.
- Aren't you thrilled?
- Should we be?
- Now, don't be cross, Betty.
Let's hear Peggy's side.
- [Mike] Well, he's good in the sack
and he likes to get high.
(robots gasp and grunt)
- Well, we've been going
steady for over three months.
Mother, Dad, we have such
wonderful times together.
- Oh my god.
- I'm in love, really in
love for the first time.
We plan to marry right after commencement.
It's as simple as that.
- [Servo] You're grounded.
- Peg, you wrote us last week
that Joe was going into
professional football.
Has he signed on with anything yet?
- Well, he hasn't got the contract yet.
But he's been told he has a
very good chance of getting one.
After all, he's been the star of our team
here this year, you know.
- Peg, your mother and
I have come down here
to ask you to put off your wedding.
- [Servo] And to kill Joe.
- Until at least after you've graduated.
Now dear, if you'll wait,
we can help you get a house
and you can set up a home properly.
- [Robots And Mike] Take
the house, take the house.
- I love Joe.
- Kill us, please kill us, slut.
- (crosstalk) wherever we're situated.
Being with Joe means more
to me than anything else.
We won't wait.
- But, dear, you only have one
year and a month more to go.
It'd be such a pity not to finish here.
- Captain Spaulding.
- And while you're
finishing your last year,
Joe can get established in football
if that's what he really wants.
And you'll have some more time to see
if you're right for each other.
- That theoretical
stuff gives me a a pain.
We're sure now we're right for each other.
And that's all that's really important.
- But Peggy, we want to meet Joe.
Now look, why don't we
all have dinner together
at the hotel tonight?
And then he can tell us all
about his football business.
(robot mumbles)
- Football is Joe's profession, Mother.
And is just as good as anything else.
- [Servo] Get a rope, honey.
- Joe and I already made
plans for a date tonight.
And I see no reason to change them now.
- But Peggy, dear-
- You're not going to stop us marrying.
Dad thinks all he has to
do is pay for something
and he'll get his own way.
- [Servo] Worked until now.
- You think by treating me like a child,
you can force me to do what you want.
You're both wrong.
I'm no child, I'm me
and I'll do what I want.
- [Servo] Well, honey, looked
like we spawned a demon seed.
(Mother whimpers)
- Don't worry, Betty, she'll get over it.
Just a touch of hysterics, that's all.
Why, by the time the end
of the semester comes,
she'll probably be madly
in love with someone else.
Come on, we'll see her
again in the morning.
- [Servo] Let's hit the
bar, it's happy hour.
- [Servo] Young Colonel Sanders.
- [Mike] He's no football player,
he might be in the swing choir.
- Oh, Joe, I'm so mixed
up about everything.
- [Crow] Original or extra crispy?
- Folks trying to stop us.
They've always tried to run my life.
- [Mike] I want you to run my life.
- Like when I wanted to go
to a dance at road house.
- Hm?
- Dad insisted that I stay at home.
- Just 'cause Patrick Swayze was there.
- I was so mad, I climbed out of a window
and went to a girlfriend's house.
- [Mike] That's kind of odd, honey.
- And the folks were frantic.
They looked all over for me.
They even called the police.
- [Crow] Finally found
me at that crack house.
(Joe laughs)
- What a girl.
If I had so many brothers and sister,
no one would miss me if I'd left.
- [Mike] Who care about you?
- It would take a couple days
for anyone to realize I'd gone.
- Well, believe me,
being an only child has
it's disadvantageous.
(Robot honks)
- Hey, move it out there.
(robots honk)
- Every move I've ever made.
Being in college has been sheer heaven.
- [Mike] Except for the classes.
- Joe, we've got to do something.
They'll do anything to break us up.
I wish I hadn't sent that telegram.
If Liz hadn't made me.
- Look honey.
- [Servo] I should tell you I'm a woman.
- I love you.
I want to marry you.
- [Mike] But what is this crap?
- Love you too Joe.
I don't ever want to be away from you.
- [Crow] We have a winner.
- [Servo] Luminary returns indicate love.
- [Mike] He's at the 40, the
50, he might go all the way.
- [Crow] Oh, you taste like Troy Donahue.
- [Servo] You taste like Elinor Donahue.
- [Mike] Oh, I'm spent.
That was incredible.
- We'll work something out.
- [Servo] Watch out for snakes.
- [Crow] Meanwhile, back
in the cold, bitter,
loveless life of her parents.
- Oh, good morning, Liz.
- Good morning, Mr Kramar.
Good morning, Mrs. Kramar.
- Good morning, Liz.
- We inquired at the desk for Peggy,
but they said she wasn't
in, so we asked for you.
- [Servo] We'd knew you'd be in.
- I don't really know Mr. Kramar.
She left the room very early this morning
before I was awake.
- [Mike] For some reason
she took her teddy.
- She left this note for me.
- [Servo] Let's see here.
Dear Dad, lose the mustache,
you twisted old fruit.
- Dear Liz, I'm afraid mother
and Dad would try and stop us.
So Joe and I left this
morning to be married.
- Oh, Mr. Drysdale, oh.
- [Mr. Kramar] Try to explain,
that this is something
I had to do.
I'm afraid they won't understand.
Love, Peggy.
- [Servo] Here, look at it.
Look at it.
- [Liz] I'm sorry, Mrs. Krammer.
- Got the boogers again, hey dear?
- Couldn't she have told
us how she really felt?
She only mentioned this boy
twice in the last in letters.
- [Mike] Look, I'm the roommate, lay off.
- I just thought it was
another college crush.
- How could she do it?
- Well, see the man
lies next to the woman,
at (indistinct).
- Even getting married at
the end of the semester
would've been better than eloping.
Poor darling.
- [Servo] Ah, let's make sweet
love and have a new daughter.
- She may have so much to regret.
- [Mike] Or she could end up like us.
- [Servo] Sorry, I can't be your daughter,
I already have parents, buh-bye.
- [Crow] Geez, I don't blame Peggy.
What a couple of wingnuts.
- [Mike] Hi, let's go talk about
our superior relationship again.
- [Narrator] Liz and Andy,
are they really in love?
- [Servo] Can love transcend gender?
- [Narrator] Is Peggy right in thinking
that Andy and Liz are too old fashioned?
- [Crow] Is this going to be on the test?
- [Narrator] What about Peggy and Joe?
They appear to be in love.
- [Mike] They're not.
- [Narrator] They're obviously
are physically attracted
to one another.
Right now, they're
radiant with excitement,
and the thrill of taking
matters into their own hands.
- [Mike] Yes, yes, yes.
- [Narrator] When this excitement
of the moment settles down
what will remain?
- [Servo] A big VISA bill.
- [Narrator] Will they be
companions as well as lovers?
Willing and able to share the realities
and responsibilities of having a home,
bringing up children, and making a living.
- [Crow] Hey, you're
bringing me down, man.
- [Narrator] There's really
no one and only for any of us.
Until we make it so by our own choice.
And when we do choose, we have to know,
will this love stand the test of time.
- [Servo] You make the call.
- [Narrator] How would
you answer this question
for Liz and Andy, Peggy and Joe.
- [Servo] Bob and Carol,
and Ted and Alice.
- [Narrator] Is this love?
- [Crow] You have ten minutes
to answer the questions.
Starting now.
- [Mike] And now stay tune for
the Clarence Thomas and
Anita Hill hearings.
- [Crow] No animals were hurt
during the filming of this movie.
- [Servo] How much affection?
- [Crow] When should I marry?
- [Mike] Know you ointments.
- [Servo] What's that down there?
- [Crow] When he wants it rough.
- [Mike] Procreation not recreation.
- [Servo] Oh no, pleasure.
- McLintock.
(1920s romantic music)
(door clanks)
(whoosh)
(door clank)
(beeping)
(door zips)
(bubbles)
(wood shut)
(metallic door shut)
(door thud)
(rattling)
(door shuts)
- Then shall I turn my
face and hear one bird sing
terribly far in the lost lands.
Now that, my little friends, is love.
(Servo sighs)
Not since Edgar Allen
Poe for the comely Helen
chronicled so eloquently
have I been so moved,
so taken, so...
- So bored.
- Hey, come on Crow,
that's one of my all time favorite poems,
it's so complete in it's beauty.
Let me read you some more stuff.
- Aw, that ain't love.
How can it be?
It's unrequited.
Plus it's got all that
longing and yearning junk.
I want to hear about hot love.
Quick and ready, you know.
See it, like it, got it.
- Like Rod Stewart sees
Rachel Hunter on TV,
writes her a letter, than
boom, they're married?
- Yeah, don't you think that's love?
- I know it is for me if
you've seen that video.
Wow.
- I'm serious.
Do you think it's love?
Or how about Eydie Gormé
and Steve Lawrence?
Is that love true?
- Well, it's love, but it's not love
on a scale of Glen
Campbell and Tanya Tucker.
- Oh no, no.
- Well, how about Emilio and Paula?
Is she forever his girl or
his he a cold-hearted snake?
- Oh, Crow, she's so cute,
and he's just as nice as the dickens,
I'm sure it can survive.
Well, just look at Don and Melanie.
Hey, no problems there.
- Well, true.
How about Bruce and Demi.
Joanne and Paul.
Oh and Kurt Cobain and Kourtney Love.
Now they've been their house
on high end solid ground.
- And as the classic Edie
Adams and Ernie Kovacs.
- Maria Shriver and Arnold.
- Jack Douglas and Reiko.
Hey, John and Yoko for that matter.
- Joan Didion and John Gregory Dunne.
- Get with it, Nelson,
show biz love is the
only love that matters.
- Oh, it is, huh?
Okay, well how about Burt and Loni? Hm?
- Oh, no I can't believe it.
Please, it's so sad.
Who would've guessed,
oh, and their little boy.
And what will become
of the dinner theater?
(Servo cries)
- Oh, good one, Nelson.
- It's like walking on
eggshells with this one.
- Eggshells, no.
(Servo cries)
(upbeat music)
- Whoa, whoa.
- Hey, oh Gucci's jamming
with Ramsey Lewis.
- I'm getting more afraid every time
I come to meet you here.
- Argh.
- Who's ever going to
find us here at school?
And anyway where else could
we go at night to be alone?
Don't worry.
- I am worried, Jimmy.
I'm afraid of something.
I don't know what it is.
- Afraid? Of who?
- Richard Speck on a date.
- Of course they'll know as long
as they think you're with Anne.
- [Mike] Does Anne do this?
- Oooh.
- [Servo] Forbidden love is the best.
- [Crow] Damn him, damn him.
- [Servo] Near the ocean (indistinct)
- [Mike] You almost
done with my boyfriend?
- Come on.
- [Crow] More tongue.
- It's late.
I've got to go home.
- [Mike] Well, kiss my grits.
- Hey, will you-
- Okay, Anne, okay, I will be right there.
Let go, no more, Jimmy.
I'll see you next Saturday night.
- [Crow] Go on, get.
- I'm sorry, Anne, but-
Oh, hello Mr. Wilson,
what are you doing here?
It's so late.
- I might ask you the same
question, young ladies.
- [Servo] Let me check my line here.
- You shouldn't be out this time of night.
- [Servo] (indistinct) time of night.
- Or any time at night
when the school is closed.
Look, I'll walk you home.
Wait right there, I'll be
right back in a minute,
I'll get my hat and coat
and turn off some lights.
I'll be right back.
- Oh, no.
- No, you don't have to bother.
Please don't.
- No, no bother at all.
You stay put right here.
I'll walk you home.
- [Crow] He asked me, he asked me.
- Come on, let's go without him.
- No wait, maybe we
ought to do as he says.
- [Mike] He is the janitor.
- Do you think he knows
about me and Jimmy?
Oh, what's the difference?
It's too late now.
Come on.
- [Servo] Now they're going
to go neck in the alley.
- Urgh.
- [Crow] Another busy Friday
night, in downtown St. Paul.
- Yeah.
- Several hours later.
(Servo sings a beat)
- My diaphragm hurts.
- I'm beginning to wish
we waited for Mr. Wilson.
- But it was your idea to leave.
- Well, we did.
- [Mike] Now, we're stuck in lake forest.
- Let's go this way.
- [Mike] I live the
other way, but all right.
- [Crow] Angels, hard as they come.
- I can't stop.
- Come on, Anne, we've got to go.
- Oh, Betty, I can't.
- [Crow] I feel very much for this pole.
- I got to rest.
- [Servo] Got to rest.
- Hey, do you hear something.
- [Mike] Sound like Ruth Underwood.
- No, I didn't hear anything.
- [Crow] I hate you.
- Look, I'm going, come on.
- Look rhubarb.
(woman screams)
- [Crow] Oh I've had better dates.
- Anne?
- [Crow] Splendor in the
Grass 2: Dream Warrior.
(Betty screams)
- [Servo] Hey would you keep it down,
I'm trying to strangle someone here.
- No.
- [Mike] Pepé Le Pew over there.
(kissing sounds)
- [Servo] With action hips.
- [Mike] Now is this a
teenager who strangles
or a person who strangles teenagers?
- [Crow] Good question, let's watch on.
- Oh, anytime Vi's a production,
it turns out so well.
- Oh my god.
- Unless it's those jerky
canned onions, and all.
- American Diversified.
It's produced by a food service.
(siren)
- [Servo] Geez look at that.
Even dead she looks great.
She can wear anything.
Oh, I hate her.
- [Crow] I think the dog did it, Ed.
- When did you find the body?
- We got a call about half
an hour ago, Lieutenant.
And then he was there and I investigated.
- I'm a guy.
- Looks like she got
it just like the rest.
- Hm.
- Yes, it's a, it's the same MO.
- [Crow] He means modus operandi.
- Lipstick mark on her forehead.
- Yup.
- [Servo] He's a humorous
killer, isn't he?
- What kind of a nut would
do something like this?
- We're still trying to find that out.
Three weeks ago, it was a
17-year-old girl in Konoba.
Last week a student teacher at the school.
Not much older than this kid.
- [Servo] Let's review the
case in front of everybody.
- Do we take her now, Lieutenant?
(woman laughs)
- It's not funny.
- Okay, Doc.
You can take off now.
- [Mike] Oh, wait, let me
gape at her some more here.
- [Crow] Ready?
(grunting)
- [Servo] Jesus, (indistinct).
Hey, move that keg out
of the way, will you?
That there thanks.
- [Crow] Yeah, yeah, she'll
fit, I'll make her fit.
There, always room.
See.
- [Mike] Well those
ambulance guy seem real nice.
- [Servo] Pump it, there we go.
(siren)
- [Mike] Yeah, there was
talk about having lunch,
but just never get to it.
[Crow] I need a Snicker bar.
- [Mike] (indistinct), please.
- Lieutenant Anderson to headquarters.
- [Servo] Anderson, that's me.
- [Man] Headquarters,
go ahead, Lieutenant.
- We've finished here, they've
taken the body to the morgue.
- [Mike] That guy's in the back seat.
- [Man] (indistinct) wants to know
if you've got any new clues?
- No, nothing more than before.
- [Crow] And don't rush me.
- It's the same one.
Tell Captain Murdoch, I'll be in
as soon as I've finished around here.
Oh, and you better have
a couple of the boys
down here to help Bill.
Are you 10-4?
- [Man] 10-4.
- Okay.
- [Crow] 10-4, that's
official cop talk, you know?
- Now, you'll have some help.
I want you to comb this whole
area, check out everything,
street houses, everything in sight.
- [Servo] But, Captain I-
- I've got some things
to attend at morgue.
- [Servo] But I'm the milk man.
Guess I'll could leave him some yogurt.
- [Mike] Well, I'll get through tomorrow,
what could possible happen
between now and then?
(siren)
- [Crow] Who cares.
- [Servo] Six-ten, I
return to the Best Western.
- [Crow] Mamie Eisenhower.
- No, (indistinct) we
don't know who it was.
- [Servo] What was that?
- [Mike] I don't.
- But it made nos sense
until this morning.
- [Mike] Yes, I explain golf.
- Yes, we called the police.
- [Servo] Yes, he's dead, dead, dead.
- As a matter of fact, we're
expecting them at any moment.
- [Crow] Six-eleven, they were
expecting us at any moment.
I ring the bell.
- The door bell's ringing,
that must be them now.
I've got to hang up.
Yes.
- [Servo] Okay, I'll join the ACLU.
- Yes, yes, I'll call your right back.
- [Mike] From community
theater to the be big screen.
- [Crow] Now remember the three S's.
Smile, star, strong.
- Oh.
- I'm Lieutenant Anderson.
Homicide division.
- [Servo] Drop the poodle and step away
from the condo please.
- Only one of you?
- [Mike] (indistinct) Wilson.
- I'm Betty's mother, Mrs. Royson.
We've been expecting you.
They'd phoned you'd come.
Let's go into the living room.
My husband's in there.
(robot laughs)
- [Crow] You're quite handsome.
Can I touch your gun?
(door closes)
- [Mike] Do we start
with stern questioning?
When do you become physical with me?
- Dear, this is Lieutenant Anderson.
- [Servo] Anderson, that's me.
- How do you do, Lieutenant?
Now, I knew a policemen
once back in my home town.
- [Crow] Didn't like him.
- His name was Hertison.
- The name I have is Anderson.
- [Servo] That's me.
- Mr. Royson, I'm here on police business.
- Sit down, would you?
(farting effect)
- Terrible thing last night.
We could hardly understand Betty at all.
- [Crow] It's the chair sir.
- Mr. Royson, I'd like
to talk to your daughter.
- [Crow] Hey, take a number, pal.
- She had a rough time last night.
I don't think she's up yet.
- Listen, she's lucky she can wake up.
Would you get Betty, please?
I'd like to ask her some questions.
- Of course, Lieutenant,
I'll get her right away.
- [Servo] God, I would trade
places with you, well, anyway.
- Do you have any idea who
it might be, Lieutenant?
How about some coffee?
- No, thank you, I'll pass this time.
From what you informed us last night,
your daughter didn't get
a positive identification?
- Well, that's what she said.
- What time did you daughter
get home last night?
- Well, I really don't know for sure.
You see my wife and I
were out at the time.
- I see.
- [Crow] Enough said.
- Yes, we were at the Fredrick.
A business meeting, you know.
- [Servo] Yeah.
- Well, the first call came in around 2AM.
Is that right?
- Well, that's when we came home.
I believe it was you
who called here later.
- Yes, sir, that was around 3AM.
- Quite a night between calls.
- I had to stay home
the day for my business.
- [Servo] I had diarrhea.
- It's frightening to
think a thing like this
could almost happen to your daughter.
- It happened to someone's
daughter, Mr. Royson.
Someone's daughter who was
out with your daughter,
until all hours of the night.
- Now, see here, Lieutenant.
- [Crow] Stick it where the sun don't-
- My daughter, she has to be in by 10PM.
We can't watch over her
like an old mother hen.
- [Servo] Bock, bock.
- Why pick on my innocent little girl
who was almost killed last night herself?
- Nobody is picking on
your daughter, Mr. Royson.
But you and every other
parent in town has known
about these attacks
and it's your responsibility
to watch out after your kids.
- And your responsibility too.
You're getting paid for it, Lieutenant.
That's your job as a cop.
- And what's your job as a parent?
- [Servo] Are you as turned on as I am?
(upbeat rock music)
- Oh, I do hope you and the lieutenant
are getting on real well.
- [Crow] Shut up.
- Betty will be down in
just a moment, Lieutenant.
Can I get you a cup of
coffee or something?
- No, thank you, ma'am.
- [Mike] May I show you my slip?
- Dear, did you tell the Michelsons
we won't be over this evening?
This has been quite a shock
to both of us, Lieutenant.
We really do feel we should
stay home with Betty tonight.
That is right isn't it, Lieutenant?
- [Mike] Easy now, almost there.
They're only stairs.
Oh no, more stairs.
- Sit down here.
- [Crow] Pardon the stain, I'm a cop.
(farting sound)
- I'd like you to tell me everything
you can about last night.
- Yes, sir, I understand.
- [Mike] I kissed my
boyfriend and the girl died.
- It was so horrible.
- There, there, dear
- Pleas, Mrs. Royson, let me handle this.
- Betty, I want you to
tell us everything you can.
In the first place.
Why did you come in so late?
- [Crow] Are you now or have
you ever been a communist?
- I was with Jimmy last night.
- Jimmy?
How many times have I told you
I don't want you running
around with that wild kid.
- Jimmy is not wild.
- Mr. Royson, let me do the talking.
- Yes, Lieutenant.
- [Servo] Jag off.
- [Crow] What was that?
- Please Mrs. Royson, I'd
like to talk to Betty.
- [Crow] Please clear the shot.
- [Mike] Looks like mom has
won some dirt track trophies.
(robots laugh)
- Betty, where were you last night?
- [Servo] I waited for you for hours.
- Well, Jimmy and I drove around a bit.
I planned to meet Anne at the school.
We were going to tell our folks
that we'd been working at the library.
- [Crow] This is hot, hot, hot.
- Anne, and I met at the
school about 12:30 - 1 o'clock.
- [Lieutenant] Betty, we're
dealing with a thrill killer.
A mad man.
If you can remember anything.
- [Mike] Punch it up a little.
Sell me this mad man.
- Lieutenant.
- [Lieutenant] Yes?
- [Servo] Yes, go on, more, more.
- It couldn't have been one of the kids.
- [Crow] They were all good Lutherans.
- Oh yeah.
- It couldn't have, could it?
- [Lieutenant] I don't know.
Whoever is, is familiar with the area.
Probably knows what most of you do.
- It's just that, oh it couldn't
have been one of the kids.
- [Servo] Okay, fine, it couldn't
- Well, the gang, the Fast Backs.
- [Betty's dad] The hotrodders,
the fast bunch he goes out with.
- [Lieutenant] Yes, sir.
What about them?
- I remember hearing Anne scream.
- [Crow] It went "Ahhh."
- And I was walking just a bit ahead.
- [Lieutenant] What then Betty?
- [Servo] She was looking at my butt.
- The club, has these white
emblems on their jackets
and well, like, I turn for just a second,
and it looked like-
- [Crow] And you became a pillar of salt.
What? What?
- Oh, it couldn't have been
one of the kids, Lieutenant,
it couldn't have.
They wouldn't hurt Anne like that.
- [Servo] Come on, stop yodeling now.
- One of them you think you saw?
- But I'm not sure.
It could've bene anything.
I don't know.
- Betty, what do you think you saw?
- A bulldog, Lieutenant.
- [Crow] McGruff?
- I might've seen a bulldog.
(50s music)
- Ah, very nice.
(indistinct)
- Give me a hot chocolate, will ya'?
- Hey, Marty, how about
two burger (indistinct).
- Coming up, Nicky.
- One (indistinct).
(indistinct)
- Timothy Van Patten's favorite hang out.
(robots laugh)
- [Servo] A square booth here.
- [Marty] Sorry, Tony, no (indistinct)
without we had a chance
to check your references.
- [Mike] Look there's a
chef appearing tonight.
(indistinct)
- It's rotten.
- Oh, shut up.
- What? (indistinct)
- [Crow] I love the atmosphere here.
- Hey, Marty, it's okay, I'll pay for it.
- Okay.
- Sit down, runt.
- [Servo] Oh, lunch at
the Russian tea room.
Joining us at the races tonight, Jim?
- I don't think so, Curly.
- Kind of figured you'd shut down.
You weren't there last night either.
- I know, but...
- What?
- [Mike] It's over, Curly.
- Either you're going to drag it,
or you're going to drop it.
- Look, why don't you just lay off, Curly.
You know what happened last night.
- [Servo] Marty, what do
you want to do tonight?
- Why you jerk.
- Betty almost got killed too.
- For the very last time, runt, shut up.
- [Crow] You're finger
smells like baloney.
- Look, Curly, why
don't you keep your fat-
- Hands off, little man.
- You can break it up in here.,
you got anything to settle.
- [Mike] Hey, Drew Carey.
- Settle it outside.
- [Crow] I breathe a little easier knowing
that Fry Cooks on the job.
- Hey, gang, come on, Jack.
- Hey it's Heidi.
- Hey I'm sorry about last night.
Berry okay?
- I haven't seen her yet.
But I guess so.
She wasn't in any of her classes today.
- [Crow] Good read, good.
- [Servo] Hey, you, dance.
- [Crow] This teen joint brought to you
by the paneling console.
- Hey, you ready, Jack?
- Almost cupcake.
- [Mike] Oh, that was great.
- [Servo] Hey, get off my toast.
- Citizens, citizens.
- Union, union.
- Don't scratch the table.
- Oh, what, bloomer.
- Fellow citizens and
lovers of good music.
- [Servo] You better leave.
- For those of you
who pledge your allegiance
to Peter, Paul and Mary.
(cheering)
- [Crow] They're dead.
- Those of you who have
undying love for the Beatles.
- [Mike] Music for 18
musicians by Steve Reich.
(cheering)
- [Mike] The dead Kennedys.
- [Crow] Circle jerks.
- Paul Langda.
- The Cramps.
- The Buzzcocks.
- Not to mention the Chad Mitchell Trio.
(indistinct)
(cheering)
- I proudly introduce
you to Mary and Jack,
the Huntington Astronauts.
- [Mike] Hey you can see the ceiling.
Gregg Toland must've photographed this.
- We're out of this world.
- [Mike] Because that's the joke, you see.
- Here's our new record sensation
just released to an RCA Victor label.
- [Crow] Look, you're standing
in my biscuits and gravy.
- Not a record, mind you, a label.
(people laugh)
- Check please.
- Ready.
- [Servo] Hope these kids
have grief counseling.
♪ I had a fella ♪
♪ Who told me ♪
♪ Nothing ♪
(robots yell and grumble)
♪ I let the new fashions unfold me ♪
- [Crow] She's the peppy one.
- Mm.
♪ My sweetie told me this is it ♪
- Whoa.
♪ yipe stripes that's the latest fashion ♪
- [Mike] White flight
♪ That's the thing to wear ♪
- [Robots And Mike] White flight.
- [Mike] This is so...
- [Servo] Hm, that's cute hair.
- [Crow] Hey, is my clone burger done?
(Mike verbalizes a beat)
(robots laugh)
- It looks like the dad from
Family Circus over there.
(robots verbalize beat)
- [Crow] Hey, even Charles
Whitman, aged nine,
got down with the funky music.
(robot verbalizes beat)
- [Crow] See all that
Charlie Callas over there.
(robot grunts)
- [Servo] You give me back my diaphragm.
- [Crow] No.
- Yes.
♪ Want a crook? ♪
♪ Who's a schnook. ♪
- [Mike] Boys must wash feet
before dancing on counter.
(robot laughs)
Patty Smith, the early years.
♪ What's he wearing now? ♪
- [Servo] Oh, mama told me not to come.
♪ yipe stripes, now you go the beat ♪
(robot hums)
♪ That's the latest craze. ♪
- [Robots And Mike] Sing pile.
- [Crow] Let's see your pantaloons again.
- [Robots] Whooeee.
(audience cheers)
- [Crow] Thank you, the
Mickey's diner audiences
are the greatest audiences
in the world, whooo.
- Maria Callas thanks Zinovia.
- [Servo] Maybe this was the
start of the counter culture.
(robots laugh)
- Love me.
- I got a tip of Oklahoma.
- [Crow] Doing the butt.
Doing the butt.
Crazy kids, look at
all these yipe stripes.
- [Servo] Oh no, no, no, no, no.
Don't tempt me, I'm happily married.
- All right, cut the
noise, cut the jukebox.
- I want a chicken salad sandwich
and I want to eat in peace.
- [Mike] Sir?
- [Robots] Yes?
- Suck me out of the room.
(upbeat rock music)
(Servo spits)
- Ay.
- This turf is mine, metal mouth.
(Crow spits)
- Nothing doing, Crow-magnets
rule the playground.
- Says who, huh?
The hovermothers own this black top,
we run this town.
- Yeah, well talk is cheap, chump.
You ready to rumble?
- I'm ready to rumble - oh,
wait, wait, wait a minute.
- Why? Why?
- I rolled in some game.
- Oh, you got-
- There I got it.
- Okay.
- Okay, tough guy, let's dance.
- You and me going around and around.
- Guys, guys, what's going on?
What are you doing?
- I'm about to show this Crow-magnet boy
who's the boss around here.
- You couldn't show Aunt
Mable the mall of America.
- Why you, I'd ought to -
- Guys.
I think this street gang
thing has gone far enough.
It's time we rapped.
- How's that?
- You know, rap, lay it out in the open.
That's dialogue.
- We were really just playing, Mike.
You know, it's make believe.
- Yeah, no big thing, Mike, okay?
- Guys, this street is in my blood.
I grew up with this stuff.
Now what's going down?
- Mike, give us break,
you grew up in Little Chute Wisconsin.
- Oh, yeah, but we had streets
and sometimes they got pretty busy too.
On a Saturday night during crazy days
and all the side walk sales were going on.
It could seem just like hell town.
- Wow, what you must have gone through.
- Well, look at that time, I got to get-
- No, no, no, nobody's
leaving 'till we figure out
what crime has been perpetrated here.
- No crime, we were just playing.
- Yeah.
- Oh, just playing, huh?
Well, that's really funny, Crow,
because I knew another little brother
who was just playing and you know what?
He bought himself a one way
ticket to the bone orchard.
Now let me take a guess here.
Servo, you dis my little
brother Crow, is that it?
- Dis as in disrespect?
- Yes.
- Oh, sure, always.
- Then you dis me too.
Because when you cut
my compadre you cut me,
and when you cut me,
you cut all men everywhere.
Am I getting through to
you guys on this, huh?
Oh, you've made made a deep impression.
(crosstalk)
- Hey, hey, hey, guys.
Come on, people now.
Smile on your brother, everybody.
(buzzing)
(indistinct)
(door opening)
(metallic door opening)
(thud)
(bubbles)
(zip)
(beeping)
(metallic door opening)
(metal door opening)
- Hey, man, don't tell
me we got another rat.
(indistinct)
- [Crow] Shut your cake hole, Nelson.
- [Servo] Thank you, I'm glad to be here.
Thank you for supporting live homicide.
- Now most of you know
what happened last night.
But we have reason to believe
that someone where might be involved.
- [Crow] Someone bring in my presentation.
- Hey, Jimmie, what's going on?
- Just don't say anything.
Betty was not with me
last night, all right?
- Okay, but I -
- Hey, young man.
- [Mike] Betty wasn't with him last night.
- Who? Me sir?
- Yes, you've got something
to say I'd like to hear it.
- Oh, no, no, no sir.
- Like, like, sir, I smell bacon.
- You, you
- Me? Me?
- You and you.
- Me and me?
- Come here.
Wait a minute.
- [Servo] Can I have this?
We need it for the cast of (indistinct).
- Who's jacket is this?
- What jacket?
(robot laugh)
- [Servo] Even, I've got to
admit, that's pretty funny.
- All right now, somebody
here owns this jacket.
- That's mine, officer.
Yeah, I hung it there when I came in.
- [Crow] You can't wear black.
- What's your name?
- Tony (indistinct).
- You're, um, you're
sure this is your jacket?
- Yes, sir, that's right.
- [Servo] Now you and I have
never met before, have we?
- How come the label says Jimmy Walton.
- Because it's mine,
Lieutenant, it's my jacket.
Here was just trying to cover for me.
- [Mike] Trying to cover up
that I kill people, he's a nut.
(robot laughs)
- All right, you five,
let's take a ride with me.
Come on.
- [Crow] Oh, jeez, yipes stripes,
what's the lit- what
the heck does that mean?
- [Mike] Yipe stripes.
- [Servo] It's visiting
day at the equipment room
at our old high school.
- All right boys, get in there.
- Excuse the masks, we kind
of live out of our jail.
- Hi, deputy, where's the sheriff?
- He's gone to the television station
to broadcast a warrant.
- Oh okay, tell him I'll him
know if there's anything new.
- Yes, sir.
- [Crow] Say hi to our TV audience.
(indistinct yelling)
- All right, hold that down
in here, hold that down.
- [Servo] Bored straight.
- Lieutenant-
- [Mike] Interrogation room in showers.
- Can't you just give us a
ticket and let's go home?
- [Crow] These pants are really tight.
- Listen, a girl was murdered last night.
Another one half scared out of her wits.
If you think this is a
comedy, you're crazy.
- [Servo] Get this, this is funny.
- Are you saying you think one of us
had something to do wit all this?
- I'm not saying anything, now sit back.
And be quiet.
- [Crow] And don't wear yellow anymore.
I'll be right back.
- Okay, boys, cavity search time.
- [Servo] Geez, not (indistinct)
no more killing all summer.
- Really bug me.
- Get if off, Curly.
- Hey, look, we know none of
us had anything to do with it.
- Yeah, but where we dragged
last night isn't sanctioned.
- It's you.
- [Crow] Jew? I specifically
heard him saw Jew.
(indistinct)
- You going to tell him where you were?
- Yeah, Curly, we could
get arrested for dragging.
- Yeah, man, we're in a mess.
- I told you we shouldn't have last night.
- Cool it.
- [Mike] The man wants us to fight.
- I got to think.
- [Servo] Well you're all to be hanged.
- You're parents have been called.
They're coming after you.
- Hey man, we're parole.
- Oh man, I'd rather stay
here than face the old man.
- [Crow] Why you, I ought to.
(robots grumble)
- Look, Lieutenant, you
still haven't told us
what this is all about.
- First I want to know how
many more in your group?
- What do you mean, sir?
- I mean this club you belong to.
These jackets.
What do you call yourselves?
- Fast Backs.
- That's a dumb name.
- Number one group in the state.
- [Crow] We can control
shipping from the inside out.
- The Fast Backs?
Well, how many are there?
- Just five, man.
But we're the best.
- [Servo] Quality since 1844.
- Best what?
- Drag, man.
None can touch us.
(car noises)
- [Mike] Wow, I'm impressed.
- Are there any more jackets like this?
- Well, lots of guys at school wear them.
But no other bulldog.
That's ours strictly.
- Knock it off, Curly.
(Crow whoops)
- It's just possible
one of you wearing these
was seen last night.
- Seen where?
- You tell me where.
- It's a game.
- Damn, sure beats facing my old man.
- What about you?
- [Mike] Surely not I, lord.
- I wasn't with them.
- Well where were you then?
- [Crow] I was in
Austria doing the rumble.
- My, my dad thought I was in my room,
but I snuck out and met my girl.
- Why were you supposed
to be in your room?
- My father found out
I joined the Fast Backs
and he grounded me.
- So you joined this group?
- Yes, sir.
- [Servo] Isn't this group the Fast Backs?
- [Mike] I think so, I thought.
- But that still doesn't account
for your whereabouts at
the time of the murder.
- [Servo] Sir, do we get
attorneys or something?
- I went on home.
- Your folks see you?
- No, sir.
I climbed back in through the window.
I mean, they didn't even
know I was gone I guess.
- [Mike] I'm late, what have I missed?
- Lieutenant, their parents are here.
- All right, but I want
you to remind their parents
we're releasing these
boy in their custody.
- Yes, sir.
- Eddie Egan.
- On your feet, boys.
- Man, I'd rather think I'd be arrested
than face my old man.
- All right, boys, follow me.
- [Mike] Time to introduce
you to your new husbands.
- Wait a minute, Jimmy.
- [Servo] You're real pretty.
- Son, you got problems.
Unless there's something
else you want to tell me.
- There's nothing I can tell you.
- [Mike] Well, sometimes I get all tingly.
- But I want your promise
no sneaking out tomorrow.
No seeing your girl, and
we'll let you go home
with your folks.
- [Crow] So I'm Gandhi now?
- [Mike] Are cops constitutionally
able to ground kids?
- And now here's Sheriff
Frankle of Kavil County
with a special message to our parents.
(robots yell)
- Parents and teenagers of Kavil county.
- [All] Here.
- Last night a a third child was victim
of a dastardly crime.
Somewhere in this city,
a mad man is preying
on teenage girls.
- [Crow] I believe it's me.
- And you're sheriff's office
are doing their best to stop it.
We urge you to not to try to take the law
into your own hands.
- [Mike] Cut it out guys.
- This is a civilized community.
All officers have been directed
to arrest anyone found-
- [Mike] You guys.
(robots chuckle)
- [Mike] Cut it out.
(Servo whispers)
- Stay safe.
- [Servo] And cable up.
- You have just heard
a special announcement
brought to you as a public
service by channel 13.
We now return to our regularly
scheduled programming.
- [Servo] (indistinct).
- Er, son, care to dance?
- [Mother] Is that you, John?
- Yes.
And I've got Jimmy with me.
- [Mother] Just a minute.
I'm turning the the (indistinct)
off. I'm coming right now.
- [Mike] I'm wearing
the french maid outfit.
- Dad.
- [Servo] Avert your eyes,
son, here comes Mother.
- I just heard the Sheriff's warning.
It's terrible, John.
- Yes.
- [Servo] Yeah, it wasn't that bad.
- And our son is involved.
- Congratulations.
- Jimmy, you?
- Mom.
- Now, young man, you get up
stairs and you stay there.
- But, Dad.
- Don't "but Dad" me.
What kind of a son have I got?
- You won't even give me a chance.
(robots snort)
- Give you a chance?
You've got a short memory.
- Hey, Mom.
- Who's that?
- Mom, can I bring some of the kids over,
oh, hi jimmy, this afternoon,
maybe we can do something?
- Mikey, get upstairs.
- [Crow] Your brother is a killer.
- [Mike] I think we found Waldo.
- Mhm.
- What did I do?
- Get upstairs.
- [Mike] You know the rules.
How did you get unchained?
- All right.
- [Servo] Anybody know him?
- Now the whole ugly
mess will come out again.
- [Mike] Hey, don't talk
about Mikey that way.
- I thought by moving to Huntington,
that I'd spare your mother
and I the embarrassment
of the neighbors knowing
that our son was thief.
But no, you had to raise hot rods.
Had to sneak out in the
middle of the night.
- John, maybe-
- Maybe nothing.
- [Crow] Yes, dear, thank you.
- Now you listen and you
and you listen straight.
You will stay in your room
from now on in.
I'll drive you to school.
I don't know what kind of a mess
this is going to turn out to be.
(growl)
- I don't know what we're going to do.
- [Servo] Curse at the starving class
- By Jupiter, you will stay
in your room this time.
- [Mike] Oh, don't involve Jupiter.
- I will drive you to school.
- No.
- Your mother will come and pick you up
and then into your room.
- [Crow] Now give me a hug.
- Now, get upstairs.
And you stay there.
- [Servo] Okay.
- [Mike] Is this love?
- And leave Mikey alone.
- [Crow] He's working on his novel.
- [Mike] I love it when you
act like der Führer, honey,
let's commit the Marriage Act.
No?
(robot snorts)
- John.
- [Servo] Marsha.
- What are we going to do?
- I don't know.
- [Crow] Let's learn Italian,
I've always wanted to learn Italian.
- I just don't know, June.
(robot fake cries)
(door knocking)
- What?
- [Mikey] It's me, Jimmy.
- [Servo] Can I have Barbra
Streisand albums back?
- Can I come in?
- No.
- Please.
- [Mike] I want to make you feel better.
- Dad said no.
- [Crow] But I've got my
TJ Friday's outfit on.
- Mom's nextdoor.
- With her head in the oven.
- Please let me come talk to you, Jimmy.
- [Mike] Will you give me a swirly.
- Please.
- All right.
But stop your sniffling.
Here.
- [Crow] The Amish kids beat me up again.
- What are you going to do?
- Rot in this room, I guess.
I don't know.
- Jimmy.
- Am I blooming?
- I'm sorry.
- It's not your fault.
- But Dad's so upset.
- Yeah.
I guess I can't blame him much.
- But it's all my fault.
- [Mike] Well only in the
sense of original sin.
- We said we'd never talk about it.
- But I got to, Jimmy, I just got to.
It's my fault you're in this mess now.
- Your fault?
You didn't sneak out last night.
- But you didn't steal that bike.
- No, and you didn't either.
- [Crow] Oh, Jimmy.
- I should've told them then.
I only borrowed it because
you wouldn't let me use yours.
I didn't steal it, honest.
- I know you didn't.
- [Mike] Is he giving birth?
- I don't know.
- Why didn't you just tell them?
- Look we promised, it's over.
- [Servo] Push, Jimmy, push, come on.
(Servo breathes sharply)
- No.
(robots yell)
- Do you think it would
make any difference now?
I'll be all right.
- [Mike] Oh, god, he's a 10.
(robots yell)
- Just leave it be, leave me be.
Get out of here.
- [Mike] Mikey's down, medic.
- Hey, I'm sorry.
(Mikey cries)
- Come one, Mikey, huh.
I'm sorry.
- [Servo] So I sing you
to sleep, after love.
- Look, do you really
want to do me a favor?
- Yes.
- [Mike] Here, put this ointment on.
- Will you take this note to Betty for me?
Only don't let anyone
see you give it to her.
- Okay.
- [Crow] It's prescription for Valium.
- You just deliver this.
- Okay.
- I'll take it to her right now.
- Hey, tell her...
- [Servo] You're really not my brother.
- Tell her I hope she's okay.
- All right.
- [Mike] And stay away
from the river front.
And no more pretending your Lord Byron.
- [Servo] Whoa.
- [Crow] Hey, it's wet here.
(robots make disgusted sounds)
(dog barks)
(robots groan)
- Jimmy, uh, girlfriend, uh.
- Clang, clang, clang went the trolley.
- [Crow] Pansey gram.
(door bell ringing)
- Mistress Isha, I'm here for my beating.
- [Mike] Okay, okay, is home Betty.
No.
Is available Betty, is Betty available,
oh, I don't know what to - ah.
- Is Betty home, Miss Royson?
It's important, honest.
I go tot talk to her.
- Well, I'll see.
You wait here.
- You'll safe our guest.
- If I could just smell a
few cushions, I'd be happy.
- [Mike] Don't lick the
furniture this time.
- Betty, Betty, Betty.
- [Betty] Yes, Mother.
- There's a young man to see you.
- [Betty] I'll be right down.
(woman gasps)
- You're in.
She'll be right down.
Wait here, young man.
- [Crow] Little freak.
- [Mike] I could really confined in her.
- Will you make me some lunch and oh.
- [Betty] Who is it?
Oh.
- What are you?
- What do you want?
- I'm sorry about what happened, Betty.
But, but Jimmy didn't do it.
- Jimmy didn't do what?
Who said he did?
- Police, they're saying he did it.
He gave me this for you.
- He was with me.
I told them that.
- [Mike] Ew, it's moist.
- Let' see, please knee
this kid in the groin.
- Mikey, tell him I'll sneak out tonight.
- [Crow] She's touching me.
- I'll meet him at Marty's.
- Okay, but he's not supposed to go out.
- I'm not supposed to see him either.
Just tell him I'll be there.
- Okay, but-
- [Mike] But what about the boom shadow
that just crossed behind us?
- I'll tell him Betty, I'll tell him.
- [Mike] Geez, what is that smell?
- [Crow] Well, that went well, I thought.
I reached out to other human
being and was not slapped down.
- [Servo] Yeah, I can chew
and dance at the same time.
(robots laugh)
- I said let's go outside
so I can strangle you.
- (indistinct)
- Hi Tony, Elaine.
- Hi.
- Hi Betty, how you feeling?
- Oh, okay, I guess.
- [Crow] My neck hurts from the strangler.
- Gee, that's a nice song.
- [Mike] It's the only song.
- Wants to give the place some class.
- Oh, shut up you're no Joey Perris.
- Hey, can I get you something?
- Oh, no, I don't think so.
- Well, how about a sip of my pop?
I mean there's nothing in it.
Am I the only drink that
can make that statement?
(people laugh)
- [Crow] I don't get it.
- Betty, can we get you anything?
- Oh, no thank you, Marty.
- Okay, how you doing, kid?
- Oooh, my Tetanus arm.
- Oho, here comes trouble.
- [Servo] Trent trouble.
(robot verbalizes beat)
- Well, hi, Betty King, how
about wrestle this one with me?
- No, I don't think so, Curly.
- [Mike] That would be strange.
- Why? I'll help you shake your blues.
- If the lady says no.
- You got a real bad memory, runt.
- [Crow] You're not good a languages.
- Now, come on.
- [Mike] Would someone
shut that music off?
It's driving me crazy.
- [Crow] I kind of like it.
- What?
I'm going to have to play teacher
and learn you a lesson you'll never forget
if you open your mouth just one more time.
Now you sit back.
- Yipe stripes, get the
the crack (indistinct).
- Why don't you let her alone,
you know she's Jimmy's girl.
- Yeah, well, Jimmy's been
grounded, so he's all cooped up.
This little bird can still fly.
- [Mike] Take it back.
Cooties.
(yelling)
- [Crow] Oh, you hurt my pant area.
- Give me room.
(indistinct yelling)
- [Crow] Get a banana split.
- [Mike] No, get the burger.
- The runt here is selected head mop.
- You'll have to start with me, Curly.
You think you're big enough.
- [Mike] You're not in Piketon anymore.
- I was only kidding.
- You and your buddies get out
of here and don't come back.
You hear?
- The service stinks anyways.
- Curly, you owe me thirty
cents for three drinks.
- Bill me.
- Where? In the hospital?
Thirty cents, cash, no credit.
- If that's okay with you.
- Randy Quaid, ladies and gentlemen.
- You and me still got a mopping date.
- [Mike] Okay, how's Tuesday?
- Out.
- [Servo] How's that, just keep? Oh, okay.
- [Mike] Well, I was
really going to get him
if he hadn't slammed me against the wall.
That really broke my momentum.
- [Crow] Ah, Gary, I broke up with you
while you were over there getting trashed.
- [Servo] The hell?
- [Mike] Peter Wellers back in town.
- Oh.
- Hi Jimmy.
- Sit down, Jimmy, I'll
see you kids later.
- What happened to you?
- Oh, nothing.
- Curly, he got fresh with Betty.
- Oh, it was nothing, Marty threw him out.
- [Crow] Slammed against
the wall again, huh?
- Look, do you two mind?
- Sure, we know, three's
a crowd, fours jam.
- [Servo] He's still
got his sense of humor.
(everyone laughs)
- [Mike] Okay, I got the stuff.
- He's really a nice guy.
- I can be a nice guy.
- So are you, Jimmy.
Oh, what are we going to do?
- Nothing.
- [Crow] Just like what we've
been doing the whole movie.
- I mean, I've got to leave Huntington.
- But why?
You didn't do anything.
- I know, but they think I did.
I've got my stuff packed.
- Where you going?
- I don't. I'll get a job
somewhere. I'll write you.
- Jimmy, please.
- [Mike] Come to terms
with your sexuality.
- You know, if my folks found
out I was with you tonight
I'd never get out again.
But I just had to see you.
- Me too.
I just had to tell you-
- Tell me what?
- [Crow] You make me feel funny.
- Someday they'll straighten out.
I'll come back, I mean,
will you wait for me?
- Oh, you know I will.
But running away isn't going to help.
- Well, what am I going to do?
- Jimmy, I love you.
- [Mike] Have the Texas toast.
- If you love me, I
don't know what I'd do.
- Me too, honey.
I got in trouble once before.
It wasn't my fault.
But now it looks like they
blame me for these things.
- [Crow] And the Hindenburg disaster.
- You know it wasn't
me you saw that night.
- No, I just saw the jacket.
Oh, I don't know what I saw.
- [Crow] You two going to order or what?
- Let me take you home.
I got to think.
Maybe if I walk or something.
♪ God bless America, land. ♪
(upbeat music)
- [Mike] Some people might not realize
that it was basically
an offensive maneuver
to let him slam me into the wall.
Oh, that's not your house.
I'm a little disorientated
after the fight and all.
- [Servo] So, do you got a water bed?
Oh, that's really safe.
- [Crow] That's the first place they look.
- I thought you said
your folks would be home.
- Well, it's a little early isn't it?
Don't worry, I'll be all right.
You want me to walk you home?
- No.
- [Mike] Well, maybe.
- You want me to come in?
- Huh-huh.
- [Servo] You can flip
any chick in the house.
Why me?
- Goodnight, Tony.
- [Mike] Oh.
- [Mike] It was the slam against
the wall thing, wasn't it?
- [Crow] Oh, by the way,
we're just friends, okay?
- [Mike] Bye.
Well, home at - wait a minute,
he dropped me off at the wrong house.
- [Servo] Goodnight Tony.
(beeping)
- [Mike] Oh, my ride's here anyway,
I couldn't kissed her anyway.
- [Crow] Nah, she won't
be strangled tonight.
- (indistinct)
(robot groaning)
(rattling of gate)
- [Crow] Mom, no, get back in there.
What have we told you.
(growling)
- [Crow] Stop it.
(robots hum)
- [Mike] God, I hate that song.
Please.
- [Servo] Let's see if King Biscuit's on.
- She's turned on the old
Yipes Stripes station.
(robots chuckling)
- That epilator is really doing the trick.
(robots beatbox to upbeat music)
- It's Gypsy Rosley and the Adventures
teaming up for the
naughtiest teen-scene ever.
- Wow.
- [Servo] She sure makes that
plaid look tasty, doesn't she?
- [Mike] She gets pretty
good sound from that radio.
- [Robot] That's great.
- [Crow] This is when
strangling was more convenient.
Strangler came right to you house.
- [Mike] In thirty minutes.
(robot grunts and grumbles)
- Watch tower.
- (robot gasps)
- [Mike] Oh, it's that
naughty Jack Tripper again.
- [Servo] Nice set of calves, huh?
- Oh, boy, mama.
- [Crow] Well I certainly
hope there's some applicators
or some non-skid surface in
that tub for safety sake.
- Oh, let me guess.
(robots whistle)
- [Mike] Oh, I'll just
change it to classic.
I can't work with this rock music.
- [woman] Hey, Mom, is that you?
- [Crow] Yes, it is.
- [Servo] Oh, steamy, sexy.
- Oh, the door.
- [Crow] Abraham Lincoln?
- [Crow] Oh, it's Andrew
Dice Clay of course.
- [Mike] Jack and Jill went up the hill...
- [Woman] Mother? Mother?
(girl screams)
- [Mike] It's my turn for the shower.
- [Crow] You're not fully dead
until your zestfully dead.
(car zooming)
(siren)
- What the-?
Convertible cop car with a siren?
(robots mimic siren)
- [Mike] Urgh, damn solar eclipses.
(indistinct)
- No, they're down the
street visiting neighbors.
- Well, is Jimmy in his room?
- Yes, Jimmy's upstairs.
He's confined to his room.
- Well, would you get him please?
- [Servo] I'm Michael Anthony.
- I'm a neighbor of
theirs, what's the problem?
- There's been another murder.
- Oh, no.
- [Crow] It wasn't me
who was murder was it?
- [Servo] Meanwhile
Teen-Boy steps into action.
Teen-Mobile away.
- [Mike] Teen-Boy is
filmed in blue vision.
- [Servo] Well he looks
like a probable suspect,
I'm going to apprehend him.
(robots mimic siren)
- [Crow] More people should
use their turn signals.
- [Mike] A daring chase scene well
within the confines of the law.
(sirens)
- [Crow] Damn you, duke boys.
(robots grunt)
- [Servo] Maybe I should
take his license plate number
and call it in or something.
(sirens)
- See the incredible school zone action.
- Okay, come on, come on, come on.
(indistinct)
- Come on.
- [Mike] So they stopped at
Henry David Thoreau's cottage.
- Teen-Boy, there's trouble
on the other side of town.
(Crow giggles)
- [Mike] You been working out?
You feel pretty good.
- All right, get the keys.
- [Servo] Could you frisk me again please?
- I'm sorry, Lieutenant, I got scared.
- Son, you scared a lot of us.
Come on, let's go, and
this time I'll drive.
- [Mike] Scaring a lot
of us is felony, son.
- (robot impersonates Elvis Presley)
- [Crow] Do they sit in the front?
It makes me feel like you're
my chauffer or something.
(Robot impersonates Elvis Presley)
- [Mike] Airport, make it snappy.
I'm just kidding, sir.
- [Servo] Get that red
(indistinct) on my car, baby.
This movie has a really gritty,
street feeling to it, doesn't it?
- [Mike] It's urban.
- [Crow] Hey you want to
stop for some (indistinct)?
- Later at Kow, Berkeley.
- [Mike] Free Huey.
- [Crow] Off the pigs.
♪ Those school girl days. ♪
- [Servo] Come here you little prodigy,
I'll give you you're mensa.
- Stop.
- Oh, look, that janitor
is into the grunge look.
- Hey, Mr. Wilson, what do you think
about what happened last night?
- [Servo] I think it's good.
- I think it's terrible.
- Oh.
- You kids ought to have better sense.
- Go about your business.
- Like you, Mr. Wilson? You
really clean up on your job.
- Jimmy didn't do anything, I know it.
- Sure, just wanted to go for a joy ride.
Kids nowadays.
- [Mike] Their hoola
hoops and ice cream sodas.
(robot grunts)
Kids is all just kids.
- [Servo] What an insightful janitor, huh?
- Angels, I want you to go
undercover as tennis players.
- [Mike] Wow, that was
good pot, wasn't it?
- Hi, Mikey, what are you doing here?
- Betty, I got to talk to you.
- Sure.
- I just go to.
- I think I'm a hermaphrodite.
- You got to help him.
- Who? What are you talking about?
- You mean you don't know about Jimmy?
- What about Jimmy?
- He's my brother.
- He got arrested last night
because he wasn't home.
Another girl got killed
and he wasn't home so they arrested him.
- I know he went home, he promised me.
- I know, but the police
came, just as you,
well he got scared and
drove off in Dad's car.
- [Mike] Don't hit me.
- When they caught him he
couldn't tell where he was,
he just couldn't.
- Oh my gosh.
He was with me.
- I know but he won't tell them.
- Oh, it's all my fault.
- Yup.
- I told him I'd get into trouble.
- Mhm.
- Betty what are we going to do.
We can't let him get blamed.
What are we going to do?
- Rub your face in crunchy underwear?
- There's only one thing we can do.
- Well I'm sorry, I...
- Come on.
- I need chocolate.
- Oh, Betty, I could beat
up in so many ways here.
(robot fake cries)
- Hey, weren't we going to
beat the crap out of him?
Ah, next time.
- [Servo] It's implied.
- Yes, Captain, yeah, we caught him,
but he won't say anything,
just that he didn't do it.
And he won't tell us where he was.
- Yes, we gave him a swirly.
- Well he says he ran off
because he was scared.
Captain, you know something-
- You're fired.
- I kind of believe him.
I don't know why, but something's wrong.
- [Servo] So what's the
other important information
you wanted to talk - hello?
- Lieutenant, there's a couple
of kids out here to see you.
- [Servo] They're waiting in my neck flap.
- [Mike] An unlikely couple.
- Betty, son.
Come on in.
- Come on, Betty.
- [Servo] We're very upset
about the school lunch program.
- Lieutenant Anderson.
- That's me.
- He didn't do it.
He didn't do it, he
was with me last night.
The reason he didn't tell you was
'cause he knew I'd get into trouble
if my folks found out that I sneaked out.
But he didn't do it, Lieutenant.
He was with me.
- And he didn't steal no bike either.
I did.
(indistinct)
- Good lord, who is this clown?
- Just clam down. Get control of yourself.
Sergeant-
- Out of here.
- And hold's these two off.
- [Servo] Beautiful scene, just riveting.
- [Mike] Great scene.
(metal door clank)
(beeping)
(zip)
(bubbles)
(chain clinking)
(door thud)
(metal door shut)
(thud)
(robots laugh)
- So, here's the plan.
- Okay.
- Mike walks into the room
- Plausible.
- Puts on those glasses.
- And thanks to a tiny electrode,
that's scrambles his left brain function,
he becomes goofy, doofy,
wimpy Mikey from the movie.
(evil laugh)
- God, I love technology.
- Oh, mama.
- Let me tell you-
- Shh, here he comes.
- Hi guys.
Hey mind if I join you?
- Hey no problem, Mike.
Always room for the blond human.
- Yup.
- That's me.
- Yeah, in fact Mike, we were wondering,
if you'd look something up in
that there dictionary for us.
- Right there, this dictionary there.
- Geez the print is small.
I how do you even-
- Well you could use those glasses
- All right.
Hey, what's with the cord?
- Um, they're digital.
- Yeah, yeah.
- yeah, digital.
- Digital?
(robots laugh)
- Well, what did you want me to look up?
- How about rime?
- Rime?
(robots snort and snicker)
- Rime.
- It's a homonym for the other word rhyme.
(robots laugh)
- I'm sorry, Jimmy, Mom's so upset.
Jimmy, you got to come back, Jimmy.
So, rime, does that help?
- Mike, you didn't finish.
- Yeah.
- I didn't?
- Rime.
- (robots snort and snicker)
- Rime, an accumulation of granula ice.
And I didn't still the bike neither.
It was all me.
It was my fault, please Betty.
Well, so that's rime.
Which is a homonym for
the other word rhyme.
You know, I think you would look good
in black glasses, Crow.
Yeah, you'd look good.
Hey, let's go clean
your head (indistinct).
- Okay, I can hold it together.
Jimmy, no, I'm me.
The sherif wants to see
you right now, Jimmy.
I'm take that letter to Jimmy.
No, I'm sorry, Jimmy.
I didn't ask for no
commercial side either.
(upbeat music)
- [Servo] Oh, incredible sexist girl man
tells all in Crime Jack.
Oh, I'm a teenage strangling man.
- You have to take the glasses off.
- What are you doing?
Oh, I'm sorry.
- Honey.
- I don't want you to be Mikey all day.
- Thank you.
- [Man] Well, if it aint' the little hero.
- [Mike] Jonathan Silvermen
- They never would've caught me.
- Maybe it's better this way.
- The offer still goes, baby.
Wanna drop slow poke here, my
chariot is gassed, and ready.
- English, please.
- Why don't you just hop in
and get on out of here then.
And take this with you.
- Ooh, and thus the
Haberdasher turf began.
- Is this a good time to mention
there's a strangler in the lose?
(bong)
- [Mike] Yeah, they're tough, aren't they?
He's the goofiest fight.
(Servo sings a beat)
- I am not a crook.
- Just another day on the
Beverley Hill 90210 set.
- [Mike] This is going to happen
when you serve tuna wiggle for lunch.
- Yup.
- Break it up.
(indistinct) to the principal.
- I'll sprinkle saw dust on all of you.
- And I'll take you on any other way too.
- Well, I get my kicks from
speed if you got the nerve.
- I got it.
- Looks like operation rescue.
(indistinct)
- I'll out run you just like before.
- Tomorrow.
- I love you, tomorrow.
- Oh, that was too easy Tom.
- [Mike] I agree.
- [Crow] Wish I had said it.
- [Mike] Now, hugs all around. Come on.
- [Crow] Oh, by the way, can
I borrow your E-Com notes?
- Jimmy, don't, your promised.
- Yeah, maybe ought to
listen to mama, Jimmy.
- Tomorrow at the strip.
- Come on, (indistinct), buddy.
- What's this Brad album
have to do with it?
- I don't know.
- Look, Katie Line is in their group.
- Oh.
- Next time we'll debate him, right?
- I don't like this, Jimmy.
- Jimmy, why do you
have to prove yourself?
- Because I'm short.
- I got it, Betty.
I guess I asked for it.
I can't back down now.
Hey, let's go to Marty's
I'll buy you a pop, huh?
- Pop, that's your answer to everything.
- Hey, Jimmy.
- [Mike] Yes, Tony?
- Don't you want your jacket?
- Nope.
Not anymore.
- It's mid July.
- Well, here you go director.
- You're fun to study with Garry.
- Next time on sweating bullets,
crime time after prom time.
- The (indistinct) new orchestra
- Excuse me, can I have a word with you?
- [Mike] Oh, Henry, please,
not every time I come home.
- Serial killing is easy
once you get the hang of it.
I'm Marshal Brody.
- Hm.
- They killed Vivian Vance.
- Oh no.
- [Mike] Every man's mom, dead.
- Ah, they're behind
you. I have that problem.
- [Servo] Suddenly it's daddy-o.
(Servo sings a beat)
- I'm trying to et the Danny
Thomas silhouette just right.
Come on, come, come on.
Okay, sit, sit, stay, stay, sit.
Come on, come on.
Sit, sit, stay, stay, stay.
- I'll meet you at the other end.
If you make it.
- We'll see.
- [Mike] How's that make you feel?
- Hey man, let's get started.
- Hunter Thompson.
- [All] Whoopee.
- And the -
- [Servo] 25 miles an hour to death.
- [Crow] They like to look at
the scenery as they drag race.
Real pretty color.
- [Mike] Jimmy pops the clutch
and politely asks the world,
would you mind eating my dust so much?
- [Servo] As a matter of
fact, I do own the road.
(robot laughs)
- Hey, youwhoo, your blinker's on.
You're blink, oh.
- [Mike] In a few years, this
whole area, all built up.
- Oh, such a shame, huh?
- [Servo] Hey, what's say about a picnic?
- Coin job.
- [Servo] I see, I see.
- Jimmy, Jimmy, stop.
I got to talk to you.
- [Mike] I haven't sold enough grit.
- Look out, that's razor wire.
- I think I'm barren now, or something.
- Mikey.
Mikey are you okay?
I'm sorry, I didn't hear ya'.
- [Mike] Is your hair on okay?
- Are you all right?
- Sure, Jimmy.
- I beat myself up.
- I'm all right.
Ma, he hardly missed me.
Mom says to call Lieutenant Anderson.
Right away.
It's important, jimmy.
- You got to go home and
empty the dish washer, Jimmy.
- I'll get to you later, Curly.
- Okay.
- Stay with him, honey.
- [Mike] Come on, there's
a sale at Laura Ashley.
- Phone, what a convenient drag race.
- The call is coming from me.
- Hello, operator, I'd like
the police department please.
- Any police department will do.
- Yes, this is Jimmy Walton.
Could I speak with
Lieutenant Anderson, please?
Thank you.
- Why doesn't Jimmy Walton call?
(phone ringing)
- Hm, the FBI didn't have
many files back then.
- Yaloo.
- Lieutenant Anderson.
- Hello, Lieutenant this is Jimmy.
- Oh, hi.
- Yes, Jimmy, now listen carefully,
I want you to get the
rest of the Fast Backs
and have them come to
my office on the double.
Nevermind.
We found one of your emblems
and I want all of you in
my office immediately.
That's right.
- His office is in the boy's bathroom.
(chuckles)
- So who wants drag race, guys?
Guys?
- Hey, Chuck, see if you
can get the guys back here.
- Us?
- You, Chuck, me?
- And action.
- [Mike] Well anyway, it's
more pride that got hurt.
At least my shirts okay.
- Quitting already?
- Look, we're all going down
to Lieutenant Anderson's right now.
- You'll be fine.
- I told him we'd all be there.
- Yeah, why you don't
promise no cop nothing.
- Don't be a fool, they found something.
Jane Housten was strangled last night.
- Oh, she was strangled last week.
- Hey Curly, where's your emblem?
- Um, my mom's washing it?
- It's in my locker, why?
- Because that's what they
found near Jane Housten.
- Oh.
- It's in my locker (indistinct).
Now look, nobody's
going to pin this on me.
- You're going with us
to Lieutenant Anderson.
- I think I hear my mom calling.
(robot grunts)
- Ooh, an able body assist from Mikey.
- Michael, I shut the door for you.
- Bye-bye now.
- Bye, kids.
- (car revving)
- Nice kids.
- No, don't you dare go through that,
don't you go through
that yard (indistinct).
- [Mike] It's the battle
of the network's sedans.
- It's junior car rodeo
with old timer Billy Sladen.
- [Mike] Can't squeal in
dirt, it's impossible.
(tsking)
- Maybe (indistinct) was
brought in to direct this.
- Too good.
(tires squealing)
- Stop that.
- Really?
(indistinct)
- It's a big pass on the rodeo clowns.
(chuckling)
- Wait, they're driving at speeds
approaching the actual speed limit.
- Mikey, would you please move over.
The other way, Mikey.
- Well at least it's a nice day for it.
(tire squealing)
- What the?
- How can he be on that side?
- Now the camera man fell over.
(crash)
- He crashed then shot himself.
(chuckling)
- Curly!
(upbeat music)
- You could learn a lot from a dummy.
They have to play the horror
(indistinct) for his accident?
- Inappropriate.
- I get his jacket.
- [Mike] You know what we have to do?
We got to pants him.
- Yup.
- [Curly] Honest, it's in my locker.
Locker.
- It looks like they're in
Vietnam all of a sudden.
- Jimmy, maybe it is.
Gosh, what have we done?
- It couldn't be.
Betty, check his locker.
- Okay.
- Tony, call Lieutenant Anderson.
- Yeah, all right.
- Ah, Curly, we'll be with you shortly.
Please standby.
- [Mike] I'm taking your car.
And I have your cheque book.
- And put some gas in it too!
And go backwards all the way.
Oh no, mIster B- Natural
is in one of those lockers.
- Oh.
- Oops.
- Friend is dying.
(robots hum)
- They have a very small student body.
- Trying to make it real compared to what.
- Oh, oh, Mr. Wilson you frightened me.
- What are you doing here?
- Oh, I'm trying to find something
or not find it or something.
- What are you mumbling about?
- I have to check Curly's locker.
- He said he left something in there.
- Oh, Mr. Wilson, it's terrible.
- Well now, we better open the locker.
Here, I have a master key.
- [Mike] We call it a master
key because every door.
One of your basic janitor tools.
It's actually quite bit of responsibility.
(chuckles)
- You been eating spaghetti-os?
(robot gasps)
- Oh my gosh.
- What is it?
- My art project.
- The emblem.
It was in his locker.
- Child, I don't have a notion
of what you're taking about.
- I've found the emblem.
Oh, Jimmy, might've killed him.
Oh, Mr. Wilson.
- Now, child, just calm down.
And we'll go to my office and
I'll fix you a cup of tea.
- Oh, what are we going to do?
- Just calm down.
(evil laugh)
- Why don't I just strangle myself then?
- I actually prefer the term custodian.
After all, I like to think of myself
as a concierge for the students.
Oh, here's where I stare
at the chair later,
it's right in here.
- Now, you sit.
- I'll strangle.
- While I'm fixing us some tea,
you tell me just what it was you found.
- Do you have camomile?
(nervous mutterings)
- Who got hurt?
- Jimmy.
I mean Curly.
You see, the emblem on
his jacket was missing
and they found one by Jane
Housten and we thought that -
he didn't.
He didn't do it.
I know he didn't do it, Mr. Wilson.
- Oh, I'm babbling I'd know - what the-?
- You know you can't wear pink.
- Oh, he (indistinct) with Malcolm Forbes.
- Oh man.
- Cool.
- This is, this is Jimmy's.
But, but, Tony through it away.
- [Mike] Lady it's time
to get on the clue bus.
- I found the jacket.
The emblem was already off.
- Oh, okay, so how about that tea?
- Is it - but when he threw it away.
It wasn't.
- Get back to us when you have
a whole sentence worked out.
- Mr. Wilson, I want to go home.
Please.
- No.
- The master wants you
but he can't have you.
- You don't want to go home just yet.
- Cream or sugar in your tea?
- Please, Mr. Wilson.
- Oh, you're saying please, Mr. Wilson.
Well all of a sudden,
it's please, Mr. Wilson.
Your bunch doesn't usually say please.
- The miss manner's murders.
- Well, Mr. Wilson won't please.
- But why? Why?
- But why?
With a student just like
you years ago, she said.
- Well, something or other, I don't know.
- I used to be a teacher then.
- Then I rolled the lawn mower.
- She said I'd tried to touch her.
I wasn't even near.
But the school board wouldn't listen.
And now look where I am.
Mr. Wilson the janitor.
You think I like it?
- Yes, no.
- You think I like cleaning up
after a bunch of grumpy kids like you?
I hate you.
- You have lovely eyes though.
- I hate you, every one of you.
- You should see a guidance counselor.
- But the jacket I saw that first time.
- I'm glad you asked that question.
- This one?
I forgot about the paint smear.
- I tried scrubbing it out.
- But in the dark it might
have look like a bulldog.
- Or a park bench.
- And that gave me the idea.
- They might have thought
it was one of you.
But no, you had to -
(woman screams)
- Fortunately, the Hagens boys
and Groover were on the scene.
- Pete, wait, ah, Tony.
- Hey, look what the janitor is doing.
- Hey.
(robots yell)
(robot whistles)
(indistinct)
- I need control top.
(scream)
- Ah, what the hell, I'll just
shoot in here (indistinct).
- What happened?
- Well he's union so they
won't be able to fire him.
- The Lysol in the...
- Punch me out please.
(gasping for air)
- Can you believe it?
Strangled with saddle toes.
(Betty gasps)
- [Mike] Ironically, there's
no one there to clean him up.
- Doh.
- He did it, he was crazy.
He killed all those girls.
- It's over, honey, it's over.
- It's all over now.
- Congratulations, it's over.
And tell her what she's won, Johnny.
- [Mike] My tummy.
- Thanks that you boys had
the good sense to call me.
- And by the way what were
you doing in that scene.
- Well that was fun.
(indistinct)
- Doh, oh.
- It's an epilogue.
- Got out of the hospital today.
- Yeah.
- It's our fault, isn't it?
- I don't know what to say to him.
- Hey look, it's Lieutenant Anderson.
- [Mike] And he's wearing pants.
- Got a friend of yours with me.
- What?
- Marty, all right.
- Okay.
- Sure.
Bring him in.
- [Mike] Maybe it's Jesus.
(indistinct)
- I got pudding in the big white place.
- Thank you.
- [Mike] Kind of embarrassing really.
Mikey beat me up.
This one's on the house.
- Thank you, Marty.
- Hey, gang, look who's giving credit.
(cheering)
- I don't get it.
- I don't either.
- Just for him, and just today.
(everyone boos)
- It's great how a serial killer
can bring a town together.
- I'll set them up for everybody.
(cheering)
- [Mike] You just stay our of the shot.
- And I'll dance with you.
Later.
- [Servo] Dancing like, the dancing?
(robot chuckling)
- I'm dancing.
- This must be the
Yikes Stripes house mix.
- Looks like he took dance
lessons from Archibald junior.
(indistinct)
(robots yell)
- I hate this.
- Will you make me food?
(robots mimic a trumpet)
- Wow, look at that butt, Bud Williamson.
(chuckling)
- Cheeky.
- I don't like this song.
Tequila.
- Oh, Danny Dean and the Daredevils.
I hope they died knowing
no body loved them.
- I can't take my eyes off of -
- I just know Mikey ended
up in Andy Warhol's factory.
- I'm the janitor now.
(robot chuckling)
- [Mike] So I thought the strangler
was going to be a teenager,
hence the title, Teen-Age Strangler.
- But he wasn't.
He didn't exactly strangle teenagers
because that one lady was older.
(indistinct)
- So why title Teen-Age Strangler.
- [Mike] Well, that exactly is my point.
(indistinct)
(metallic door shut)
(beeping)
(zip)
(bubbles)
(chain shake)
(door thud)
(metallic door shut)
(thud)
(door shut)
(robots laugh)
- This is going to be the
best Thanksgiving break ever.
- Oh, you bet ya'.
I can't wait to get home.
Bye, Mr. Shalafski.
(Mike laughs)
- Goodbye kids.
♪ The bell has rung, school is out ♪
♪ The kids have all gone home ♪
♪ All I do is sweep and pout ♪
♪ I'm left here all alone ♪
♪ I make sure the hallways are gleaming ♪
♪ I keep all the garbage at bay ♪
♪ But inside my heart will be screaming ♪
♪ How did I end up this way? ♪
♪ I'm a janitor ♪
♪ A janitor ♪
♪ I clean up the puke at your school ♪
♪ A large fistful of sawdust ♪
♪ Is my essential tool ♪
♪ I'm janitor ♪
♪ A janitor ♪
♪ I start work early each morn ♪
♪ I have a drinking problem ♪
♪ And large collection of porn ♪
♪ I'm a janitor ♪
♪ A janitor ♪
♪ I'm looked on as kind of leach ♪
♪ But at least I get more respect than ♪
♪ The ones who have to teach ♪
♪ He's a janitor ♪
♪ A janitor ♪
♪ Please don't sell him short ♪
♪ If you get him too mad ♪
♪ I'll show you my disgusting wart ♪
(robot make disgusted sounds)
♪ He's a janitor ♪
- Yeah, I'm a janitor
♪ A janitor ♪
♪ You got a problem with that? ♪
♪ He needs to be loved and respected. ♪
♪ He once dated Josephine the plumber ♪
♪ And guess what? ♪
♪ Yeah, I was rejected. ♪
♪ Go figure ♪
♪ He's a janitor ♪
♪ A janitor ♪
♪ Yeah, I'm a janitor ♪
♪ We both think he's pretty keen ♪
♪ I hope you liked our presentation ♪
♪ Now back to Deep 13. ♪
- Oh, good one, Mike.
Frank was swayed to your
little song there and got sick.
How sick?
That's your dinner for the
next three weeks, Frank.
(zoom)
(soft synthesizer music)
- And he didn't steal no bike neither.
I did.